[ Watch on KissFlix.co ]
Characters, actions, places, occupations, and events in this series
are fictional and created for entertainment purposes only.
They are not intended to urge or promote any behavior in the series.
Viewer discretion is advised.
We met before?
It happened ten years ago.
It’s not surprising that you forgot it.
But you remember me.
You’ve never forgotten me.
Key, will you be my girlfriend?
You got a tattoo?
It’s pretty.
I like it.
It’s really over.
From now on,
you don’t need to worry anymore.
Key.
Wait.
Mom.
How could you do this?
You are ruining our reputation.
What did I do?
How dare you talk back to me?
It’s true.
What did I do wrong?
Why did you get a tattoo?
Do you think this is appropriate?
It’s just a tattoo.
It doesn’t define my worth, Mom.
-Chan. -Excuse me.
Even though she’s your daughter,
you shouldn’t use violence with her.
It was you, wasn’t it?
You interrupted and cut the meeting short the other day.
Yes, it was me.
Who do you think you are?
How dare you meddle in the work of my hotel?
Do you want to show off that you’re my daughter’s sugar baby?
I’m sorry for meddling in Chan’s work.
I’ll be more careful next time.
But I’m not Chan’s sugar baby.
Chan and I are dating.
You are an outsider.
Get out of this room.
I’m going to talk to my daughter.
No.
She’s not going anywhere.
Why are you acting like this?
I’ve never taught you to behave like this.
Why have you changed?
I haven’t changed, Mom.
I’m just not afraid to be myself.
I just chose to do what is best for me.
Best to you? How?
Tell me how?
Mom, please leave.
Are you telling me to leave?
What’s wrong with you, Chan?
-I just don’t want us to fight. -Then tell her to leave.
Are you taking sides with an outsider instead of your family?
Soon, she will become a part of our family.
No.
This girl is not good enough for you.
She’s not good enough for anyone in our family.
Can you let me decide who is good enough for me?
Mom, please leave.
I don’t want to fight with you anymore.
Chan.
Mom.
Key, are you okay?
I’ll handle it.
Come on, Mom. Let’s go home.
Please, I’m begging you.
Let’s go home.
Mom.
Yes.
Sun.
Yes?
I need to talk to you.
What is it?
I can’t let your sister ruin our family’s reputation.
You need to help me and talk some sense into her.
How could I do that?
To be honest, Key seems like a nice girl.
She came from a well-known family.
But her mom is the second wife.
You don’t know how scandalous her mom was.
She had a long list of bad behaviors.
I think her daughter is not much different from her.
They are two different people.
We shouldn’t judge them.
Of course, we can.
The apple doesn’t fall far from the tree.
Because children learn from their parents.
Mom, I’m her twin sister.
I can tell that she is serious about her.
One more thing:
it doesn’t matter what kind of person Key is.
I think Chan has thought it through before dating Key.
If that were the case, I wouldn’t have been worried.
But she is serious about her. She’s even thinking about marrying her.
I can’t let it happen.
I have to stop this.
Mom.
Chan has never disobeyed you.
She always does everything you tell her.
This is not a big deal.
Can’t you let her do what she wants for once?
No.
I can’t let it happen.
My mom is the real last boss.
She is worse than Jay.
She is so self-centered.
You need to be careful.
I don’t know what she will do next.
She has never backed down.
So you met Mommy?
Then…
the fun has begun.
Who did you call Mommy, Jay?
Madam told me to call her Mommy.
She is close to your aunt.
She probably said that for the sake of their friendship.
Stop thinking that you are important to her.
Then…
good luck.
Hello.
I think you should get to the point.
What do you want to say to me?
Are kids these days like you?
No.
Everyone is different.
It’s just that…
if we know that
someone is trying to pick a fight with us or look down on us,
kids these days won’t put up with it.
You are disrespectful.
But I don’t use violence with anyone.
I fight back with reasons.
Reasons?
You are just talking back to me.
It depends on whether you are willing to listen to me or not.
If you are not,
you will view it as me talking back to you.
You know what?
No kid has ever talked back to me like this.
Jay grew up in Western culture.
She’s always respectful to me.
Unlike you.
Has she seen you slap your daughter?
If she saw it,
she wouldn’t have been respectful to you.
Now, I’m certain
that you and I can't coexist.
You are not good enough for my family.
I think you should leave.
There’s no point in trying to make it work.
You two will end up breaking up anyway.
I will never break up with Chan because someone tells me to do so.
The only way I will leave her is if she asks me to.
Do you think Chan will choose you?
When it’s time for her to choose,
do you think…
you are good enough for Chan?
Do you think
you are different from your mom?
All the scandals about your mom.
Her uncontrollable temper.
Your mom was ill.
How can you be sure that you won’t have the same illness?
You will damage Chan’s reputation.
Just like your mom did.
Key.
Let’s go.
Chan.
You can’t do this to me.
Are you crazy?
Mom.
I love you.
But I’m asking you.
Please stop saying hurtful things to the woman I love.
If you won’t stop,
I’ll have to protect my girl.
Let’s go, Key.
Chan.
It’s good that Sun called to tell me about it.
I couldn’t tell what would happen if I weren’t there.
Even if you weren’t there, I could handle it.
Why didn’t you tell me?
If my mom does something like this again, you need to tell me right away.
Don’t go to meet her alone.
I like it
when you are protecting me.
I promise.
I will never let anyone hurt you again.
I’ll protect you for the rest of my life.
Do you love me that much?
Of course.
Now, I feel a bit bad.
Why did you say that?
I just feel like…
I’m causing you a problem,
and I'm making you stressed about protecting me.
Don’t worry about that.
All I want is that you never let my hand go.
Hello, Mommy.
-Hello. -Have a seat.
Madam wants to talk to you.
What do you want to talk to me about?
Aunt, you should have called me. So I would have hurried back home.
It’s okay, Jay.
I can wait for you.
What do you want to talk about?
She needs your help.
Help with what?
It’s something I’m sure you will be willing to help with.
Is it about Chan?
Yes.
I don’t think Key…
is a good match for my daughter.
My daughter deserves someone better.
Yes.
I agree with you.
What do you want me to do?
You just get between them and break them up.
I tried,
but I failed.
Are you going to give up?
Chan is so into that girl.
She doesn’t listen to anyone, not even me.
She doesn’t listen to me either.
I didn’t want to give up.
But I know Chan well.
Right now,
she insists on being with Key.
You two were in a relationship.
I’m sure she still has some feelings for you.
If you keep pursuing her, there will be a rift between them.
You want me to cause a rift between them?
Can I ask you something?
Yes.
What if…
Chan broke up with Key,
would you support my relationship with Chan?
Of course.
Would you support us getting married?
I think…
talking about marriage is a bit too far.
I know that
you will never support Chan in marrying a woman.
Jay, you overthink it.
She didn’t say that.
I’m not stupid.
I can tell.
So…
I refuse to help you.
I won’t do it.
Jay!
I told you.
I will never let anyone boss me around again.
Mommy.
I’m sorry.
Excuse me.
I’m so sorry, Madam.
I’ll talk to her again.
Thank you.
I think I’ll need a backup plan.
Actually, I have an idea.
Do you think you are different from your mom?
Her uncontrollable temper.
(I told you to stop crying.)
(Don’t you hear me?)
(Stop crying. Don’t you hear me?)
(I don’t want to hear you crying.)
(Stop it right now.)
-Key. -I'm sorry.
(I don’t want to hear it.)
Key. Key.
(Don’t you hear me?)
Key.
Key, wake up.
(I told you to stop crying.)
Key. Key.
Key.
It’s okay.
It’s just a bad dream.
Why did you stop?
Keep practicing.
Why did you tell me to come with you?
Can you focus on your work?
If you weren’t here with me, I wouldn’t be able to concentrate on work.
I told you.
I’m fine.
I just had a bad dream last night.
What was the dream about?
Why didn’t you tell me?
See?
Something is bothering you.
But you refuse to tell me.
It’s not a big deal.
I’m really fine.
Hello, Phu.
Hello, Key.
It’s good that you are here.
Why?
Your girlfriend asked me to help prepare a surprise for you.
A surprise?
What is it?
Thank you.
Let me see.
Don’t you think it’s a bit too much?
Do we need to do this?
A photoshoot to celebrate two weeks together?
It’s not too much.
You are my girlfriend.
Let’s take pictures.
We are ready.
Get a bit closer.
I’ll shoot close-up pictures this time.
So romantic.
I feel shy.
Don’t be shy.
Peach, take a lot of good pictures for us.
Sure.
Act cool.
Pucker your lips.
Great.
Hold on, Peach.
Something is missing.
What?
Here is your prop.
Key, smile.
Look at this camera.
They are cute, Peach.
They are beautiful.
I like every picture.
Peach, do you know this?
Chan barely praises anyone.
Thank you for liking my work.
Shall we post the pictures?
Right now?
Are we going public with our relationship?
Yes.
It’s better that we reveal it ourselves, instead of appearing in gossip news.
The pictures will come out pretty.
If you are going public, it will create a buzz.
It’s creating a buzz.
But it’s not a good one.
You are too late.
HOTEL CEO 'CHAN' DATES DAUGHTER OF LATE SHORT-FUSED ACTRESS
The bad thing is…
people are digging into Key’s past and her mom.
It’s okay.
HOTEL CEO 'CHAN' DATES DAUGHTER OF LATE SHORT-FUSED ACTRESS
See?
I told you that girl and her mom have a bad track record.
You and Chan are also dragged into this.
It’s just gossip news.
Don’t pay attention to it.
We can’t do that.
Didn’t you read the news?
Her mom, Pin, was mentally ill.
What if the illness is passed down to her?
Wouldn’t it be a problem?
Mom, you are overstating.
No, I’m not.
I remember Pin was a celebrity, and she was a troublemaker.
There were scandals about her losing her temper and having outbursts.
She lashed out at staff on the set.
She also left the set for no reason.
She was lucky that her husband, Mr. Pasin, helped cover it up.
Otherwise, there would be more scandals about her to talk about.
I think she was a piece of work.
I’m afraid that her daughter won’t be much different.
Why do you know so much about her?
I’ve never seen you be this interested in anyone.
Can I ask you for real?
Are you behind this?
No.
The scandals about Key’s mom were widely known.
After she killed herself,
people became more interested in them.
I remember reading the news.
It said her daughter was the first one who found her body.
Really?
I feel so bad for Key.
Why do you feel bad for her?
Mom!
She is also a piece of work.
Didn’t you read the comments?
They said she’s a tramp.
She is scandalous, just like her mom was.
Sun.
Believe me.
I’m good at reading people.
I’m sure she will cause a problem for our family,
especially for Chan.
Mom, don’t be so judgemental.
You don’t like it when other people are judging you, right?
So we shouldn’t do that.
I don’t think it’s a good thing.
Mom?
Who’s that?
Who are you?
What do you want?
Why did you come back?
Why did you come home?
Mom killed herself because of you.
Mom hated me because of you.
It’s all your fault, Key.
Chan will die because of you.
It’s your fault. Because you came back.
Why did you come back?
Get out.
Get out. Why did you come back?
It’s your fault.
Everyone will die because of you.
It’s all your fault.
You were the reason why Mom was dead. Everyone will die because of you.
Chan will die because of you.
Everyone will die because of you.
Mom killed herself because of you.
Mom hated me because of you.
You killed Mom.
-I’m sorry. -It’s your fault.
If you didn’t come back, Mom wouldn’t die.
I’m sorry.
Get out. Why did you come back?
Why did you come back?
Key, get out!
Key.
Key. Key.
It’s okay.
It’s just a bad dream.
She’s back, Chan.
Something bad will happen.
Who, Key?
Who is back?
Come to work with me tomorrow.
But you have a meeting tomorrow.
I’ll be fine.
Don’t worry.
You should go to work.
How can I not be worried about you?
If you don’t come to work with me,
I will feel uneasy.
Don’t worry.
No matter what happens,
I will be by your side.
Yes.
Chan, you should go back to sleep.
Otherwise, you would wake up late to work.
Let’s go back to sleep.
Are you doing this to pressure me?
I have to protect our hotel’s interests.
I’m not sure if you are in your right mind enough to effectively run the business.
I’m not in my right mind?
The executives informed me
that you walked out of the meeting because of Key.
They were upset about it.
Mom, the meeting took too long.
Everyone in the room seemed to be too tired.
Was it okay to wrap up the meeting when you hadn’t reached a resolution?
From now on,
I will attend every meeting.
I’ll help you manage the hotel.
Do as you want.
Then let’s go to the meeting.
♪ If love is just a game between you and me ♪
♪ I’ll make sure I’m the one with the victory ♪
♪ I want everything my way, make you agree ♪
♪ Your heart must belong to me ♪
♪ Just hold my gaze a little longer ♪
♪ Move your heart a little closer ♪
♪ Let’s take the meaning of love a little further ♪
♪ What we have doesn't end tonight ♪
♪ I’ll love you every day ♪
♪ Close to me, your only one ♪
♪ I’ll make you love me, make you remember ♪
♪ I’ll keep repeating till you surrender ♪
♪ With every touch, remember only me ♪
♪ I’ll hold you close in everything I do ♪
♪ Make it sink in, make you remember too ♪
♪ Slowly let your feelings run free ♪
♪ You’ll remember no one else but me ♪
♪ Ohh Ohh ♪
♪ I wanna be your only one ♪
Chan.
Miss Chan.
Chan, are you okay?
I’m okay.
I feel much better.
Are you sure?
Why don’t you go see a doctor?
It’s okay.
I just passed out. I’ll be fine.
Miss Chan, how are you feeling?
I think you should go see a doctor.
I’m fine.
The meeting took too long.
So I didn’t eat anything.
I’m not feeling good about this.
You have never…
Game.
I’m fine.
Got it.
I’ll go find something for you to eat.
Yeah.
This is my fault.
I’m the reason you are sick.
No.
You are overthinking.
I saw her in my dream again.
You saw what?
What are you talking about?
Key.
Key, what’s wrong?
What did you see in your dream?
What are you talking about?
Key.
Are you alright?
Why did you suddenly zone out?
What did you say earlier?
What did you see in your dream?
I’m fine.
It’s nothing.
Key.
It’s really nothing.
It’s nothing.
I’ll go get water for you.
Chan, why don’t you rest?
I’ll be right back.
Key.
Key, sweetie.
It was your fault.
It was your fault, Key.
It was your fault, Key. Everyone will die because of you.
Mom hated me because of you.
It was your fault, Key.
-Why were you even born? -Mom hit me because of you.
-It was your fault. -I was hurt because of you.
Why were you even born?
Mom hit me because of you.
-Everyone will die because of you. -Everyone will die because of you.
Everyone will die because of you.
Mom.
It was your fault.
It’s because you came back.
Why did you come back? Get out.
Mom, it’s not true.
Key.
Chan.
It was your fault.
Everyone will die because of you.
Mom didn’t love me because of you.
Mom hit me because of you.
It was your fault.
Everyone will die because of you, Key.
It was your fault. It was your fault.
I was wrong.
Why did you come back? Tell me why you came back.
I’m sorry.
Chan, I’m sorry.
WHY DID YOU TURN OFF YOUR PHONE?
(Hello, sis.)
Sun.
Key disappeared.
(Since when?)
I’m not sure.
I woke up and couldn’t find her.
She turned off her phone.
I sent her messages, but she didn’t read them.
Key has never done this before.
I’m so confused.
I don’t know what’s going on.
(Sis, calm down.)
(Why don’t you talk to Peach?)
Okay.
I’ll call Peach.
(Please keep me posted.)
Okay, I will.
Peach.
Yes, Madam.
You just keep pressuring her like this.
Chan will give in one day.
There’s been a lot of backlash.
Key’s past behaviors are quite scandalous.
She is the black sheep in her family.
She is surely not good enough for Chan.
Yes.
If there’s anything else I can help you with,
please let me know.
Yes. Goodbye.
You scared me.
You showed up out of nowhere.
What did you do?
I’m just helping Madam Chanya.
You refused to help her.
Why are you getting involved in her business?
Jay, what I’m doing will benefit us.
If we help her now, she will help us in the future.
Can you please stop doing this?
Why?
What I’m doing is good for you.
You don’t like that girl either.
But I’ll never ruin anyone’s life.
If we don’t do this, you will lose.
I don’t want to see you come home drunk every night.
I’m worried about you. I don’t like it.
I’m worried about you.
I’m trying to help you, Jay.
I love you.
But can you leave me alone?
I don’t need your help.
Key used to have bad dreams when she was young.
I thought it was gone.
Every time she has this dream, she always runs away.
Do you know what her dream is about?
Why does she always disappear when she has the dream?
After her mom died,
she started to have nightmares.
She saw herself in the dream.
But it was not her.
It was Key who was lonely
and scary.
Key told me
it was the shadow that kept haunting her in her dream.
It kept telling her to leave everyone.
It blamed her that it was her fault
and that she was bad luck.
She was the reason why bad things happened…
to her mom and everyone she loved.
I feel really bad for her, Chan.
Since her mom died,
she kept blaming herself
for being the reason why her mom decided to kill herself.
It was not her fault.
Pin had had mental problems for a long time.
Her condition was getting worse
when she was pregnant with Key.
Pin believed that her life was ruined because she gave birth to Key.
Aunt Pin was unstable.
Sometimes, she hurt Key.
She always told Key to get out of the house.
Sometimes, she took Key out and left her.
Key had to find her way home by herself.
It was like she wanted Key to be away from her.
So she wouldn’t hurt Key.
Every time that Key found her way home,
Aunt Pin’s condition would get worse.
I tried to help Key’s mom get help from doctors.
I guess I didn’t do a good job.
It’s my fault that things turned out this way.
I hurt this family.
When I was in college,
I met Key in the mountains.
I went there to watch the stars.
I found her walking alone in the forest.
Hey, are you okay?
You are the one who saved her back then?
It’s such a small world.
Maybe it’s their destiny.
So Key was left in the forest
by her mom?
Yes.
At the time, we were looking everywhere for her.
But we couldn’t find her.
Suddenly, she came home.
She refused to tell us what happened.
(Chan.)
(What?)
I…
When I’m older,
I’ll get a moon tattoo…
here.
(You still haven’t told me)
why you got the moon tattoo.
Maybe one day,
our paths may cross again.
This will help you remember me.
After she got home that day, she was blaming herself.
Why?
Not long after that,
Aunt Pin decided to end her life.
Key was the first one who found her body.
After that night, she was haunted by the picture.
She kept having bad dreams about it.
She’d seen a psychiatrist for a long time
before she got better.
Even so,
she decided to move out and live on her own.
She probably doesn’t want to live in the house
that reminds her of the incident.
All we can do is wait.
We pray that she will be ready to come home one day.
I thought that she was fully recovered.
Is there anything we can do to help Key?
Do you know where she might be?
She ran away from home several times.
She didn’t contact us at all.
When she felt better,
she would come back.
We should go and look for her.
Yes.
I’ll help you.
(Where are you, Key?)
(I’ll find you.)
Hello, Key.
(Where are you? Are you okay?)
Can you not tell Chan about this?
I don’t want her to see me like this.
Cancel today’s meeting.
Where are you going?
I’m going to find Key.
How dare you show up here?
Do you know that your mom asked me to steal Chan from Key?
But I refused to do it.
Liar.
You spent ten years looking for me.
I’ll find you even though I don’t know where you are.
I will take you home.